#### Personal info

**3** 8726621626

arjanagarwal20@gmail.com

Lucknow

### Links

in www.linkedin.com/in/arjan-agarwal

www.hackerrank.com/arjanagarwal20

github.com/ArjanAgarwal

#### Skills

() HTML

O css

O JS

O AWS

() Java

() SQL

O MS OFFICE

#### Languages

A ≠ English

Al≆ Hindi

## Badges





# Arjan Agarwal

Web Developer | AWS Engineer

A goal-oriented graduate with strong communication, problem-solving, and leadership skills in Computer Science Engineering. Passionate web developer with knowledge of HTML and CSS. Proficient in AWS (Amazon Web Services), with experience in cloud computing solutions and services.

Work Experience \_\_\_\_\_

Web Development Intern, Technosys Services Private
Limited

June 2023-July 2023

 Crafted a ChatGPT-inspired clone with HTML and CSS, delivering a sleek and user-friendly interface

AWS Intern, F13 Technologies March 2023-June 2023
 Designed scalable and highly available AWS

architectures for various projects

Web Development Intern, Oasis Infobyte April 2023-May 2023

 Created a landing page , personal-Portfolio using HTML,CSS

#### Certifications —

Web Development - Internshala

Cloud computing with AWS - Internshala / Brillica Service

AWS Partner: AWS Cloud Practioner Essentials

Education ———

**B.Tech, DIT University** 

September 2020-June 2024

Intermediate, Spring Dale College

March 2019- February 2020

Marticulation, Spring Dale College

March 2017- February 2018